Come on.
هيا.
Second Young Master gave it to me.
أعطاني السيد الشاب الثاني إياه.
I didn't have time to give it to you just now.
لم يكن لدي الوقت لإعطائها لك الآن.
It's so cute.
انه جميل للغاية.
The color is warm
اللون دافئ
and easy to carry.
ويسهل حملها.
Ceramic knife,
سكين من السيراميك،
is it suitable?
هل هي مناسبة
It looks good.
إن شكلها جيد.
Soft and tough,
لينة وصعبة ،
long whip.
سوط طويل.
Give it back
أرجعها
to me. You're a girl,
إلي.  أنت فتاة،
Why do you always think about knives and guns in your head?
لماذا تفكر دائمًا في السكاكين والبنادق في رأسك؟
I wonder what your brother-in-law was thinking
أتساءل ما الذي كان يفكر فيه صهرك
when he sent you here?
عندما ارسلك الى هنا
You're crazy.
انت مجنون.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
He's just sick.
إنه مجرد مريض.
The point is, is there something wrong here,
النقطة المهمة هي ، هل هناك خطأ ما هنا ،
or is there something wrong here?
أم أن هناك خطأ ما هنا؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Take it to work.
خذها إلى العمل.
Let him be jealous,
دعه يغار
not to mention that I didn't help you.
ناهيك عن أنني لم أساعدك.
What?
ماذا؟
I'm touched.
أنا متأثر.
Give me back my pen.
أعد لي قلمي.
Woman,
النساء،
your name is Ruthless.
اسمك لا يرحم.
My Lord.
ربي.
She likes drumsticks and flowers.
تحب أفخاذ الطبل والزهور.
All the girls like to be praised.
كل الفتيات تحب الثناء.
I remember it very well.
أتذكر ذلك جيدا.
I don't need to do it next time.
لست بحاجة للقيام بذلك في المرة القادمة.
Yes.
نعم.
His Lordship is ready.
سيادته جاهزة.
Fresh flower juice.
عصير زهور طازج.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Clean it up,
نظفها،
Yes.
نعم.
His Lordship is wise.
سيادته حكيمة.
Brother,
أخ،
Sister,
أخت،
Where's Big Brother?
أين الأخ الأكبر؟
I don't want you to be bored.
لا أريدك أن تمل.
I brought you some scripts to relieve boredom.
أحضرت لك بعض النصوص لتخفيف الملل.
One.
واحد.
Two books.
كتابين.
Three books.
ثلاثة كتب.
Thank you, bro.
شكرا اخي.
Don't thank me.
لا تشكرني.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
these scripts,
هذه النصوص ،
I didn't find them.
لم أجدهم.
Sister,
أخت،
a man,
رجل،
Good face. If you give me a step,
وجه جميل.  إذا أعطيتني خطوة ،
he'll roll down right away.
سوف يتدحرج على الفور.
Why don't you give me a sachet too?
لماذا لا تعطيني كيسًا أيضًا؟
What gift is good for your husband on Shangyuan Festival,
ما الهدية الجيدة لزوجك في مهرجان Shangyuan ،
as long as you send it to your home
ما دمت ترسله إلى منزلك
in a sachet of 9. 9 yuan.
في كيس من 9. 9 يوان.
have a look
الق نظرة
Who wants to give him a sachet?
من يريد أن يعطيه كيس؟
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Miss,
يغيب،
guess what it is?
تخمين ما هو عليه؟
Flower cake,
كعكة الزهرة
my lady,
سيدتي،
If you used your brain on divorce,
إذا استخدمت عقلك في الطلاق ،
we would have been abandoned long ago.
كنا قد هجرنا منذ زمن بعيد.
My dear girl,
فتاتي العزيزة،
your lady has been divorced.
لقد تم إطلاق سيدتك.
What's in it for you?
ما في ذلك بالنسبة لك؟
You,
أنت،
Husband
الزوج
How can you take it back if you gave it to me?
كيف يمكنك استعادتها إذا أعطيتها لي؟
What a cheapskate.
ما هو رخيص.
Don't you already have one?
أليس لديك بالفعل واحدة؟
That's different.
هذا مختلف.
Choose one from the other,
اختر واحدًا من الآخر ،
Chuan Gu.
تشوان جو.
Thank you, my husband.
شكرا لك يا زوجي.
Is it sweet?
هل هو حلو؟
Dear, have a taste.
عزيزي ، تذوق.
It's sweet.
انه حلو.